

0

www.linkedin.com/in/kya whtetthu



https://kyawhtetthu.com/



Malaysia



htankhaishan@gmail.com



+60 18 235 3639

KEY SKILLS

MySQL, JS, PHP



Word-Press, Bootstrap, SEO



Linux

Basic Penetration Testing



- Willingness to Learn
- Adaptability
- Creativity
- Critical Thinking
- Problem-Solving
- Active Listing
- Effective Communication
- Teamwork
- Time Management

KYAW HTET THU

Cyber Security Student and Enthusiast

EXECUTIVE SUMMARY

Currently studying Bachelor of Science in Computer (Cyber Security), first year. Worked as freelance web-developer and Assistant Manager. Highly interested in Technology and love to work cohesively with team members. Be able to overcome pressures and be a punctual problem solver.

ACADEMIC BACKGROUND

October 2019 – September 2021

Scottish Qualifications Authority (SQA)

Higher National Diploma (HND) in Business Management

June 2022 – Current (First Year)

ASIA PACIFIC UNIVERSITY (APU)

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science (Cyber Security)

WORK EXPERIENCE

Freelance Web Developer

Travel Agency and Seaman Job Search company

2016 - 2017

- Develop, test, and implement the websites.
- Resolve complex technical design issues.
- Test, maintain and recommend software improvements to ensure strong functionality and optimization.
- Analyze user requirements and convert requirements to design documents

Assistant Manager

HIGH FATE Good Brothers Co., Ltd, Yangon, Myanmar

2018 - 2021

- Review and proceed the documents of the company which relate to Government sectors.
- Organize and schedule meetings and appointments.
- Manage relationships between Service Providers and Organization.
- Perform review and analysis of the projects and keep the management properly informed.
- Design and implement filing systems.